Thomas Wiltshire

Hello, my name is Thomas. I'm a hard-working, passionate programmer that is currently living in Ferntree Gully, Victoria, Australia. Over the last 3 years, I have been studying at the Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE) to obtain a Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds (Programming).

Location: Dorset Road, Ferntree Gully, VIC 3156

Contacts: +61 466661042 thomas.wiltshire14@icloud.com

Portfolio: thomaswiltshire.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds, Academy of Interactive Entertainment — *Melbourne*, *Victoria*

January 2017 - December 2019

Primary School / High School, Kyabram P-12 College / Kyabram St Augustine's College — *Kyabram, Victoria*

January 2002 - December 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Trainee, Advance Computing — *Kyabram*, *Victoria*

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at Advance Computing for around a year where I started a Certificate 3 in Information Technology as a part of my traineeship in software development. I learnt a lot during my time here, had many amazing experiences, obtained a greater knowledge of business and got my first real taste of the software development industry.

Crew Member, Mc Donald's Australia — Echuca, Victoria

March 2015 - January 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at McDonald's within the kitchen environment, being trained in most aspects. During my time here, I gained irreplaceable skills and experience in teamwork, punctuality, leadership, cooking and cleaning.

IT Technicians Assistant (Work Placement), Kyabram Community and Learning Centre — *Kyabram, Victoria*

March 2014 - December 2014 (½ Year)

As a part of my VCAL studies, we were required to find work placement. I worked at KCLC in the IT department, helping with various repair jobs, network issues and general computer assistance.

EXPERIENCE AND SKILLS

Punctual, polite and enthusiastic.

Teamwork and troubleshooting skills and experience.

People skills and great verbal communication.

An attention to detail and situational awareness.

Dishwashing, cleaning and cooking equipment skills and experience.

Understanding of food handling, health and safety standards.

A willingness to learn and experience new things.

Extensive computer and technological knowledge, skills and experience.

REFERENCES

THIS IS A PUBLIC LOCATION/WEBSITE!

IN ORDER TO PROTECT
REFERENCE INFORMATION
YOU WILL BE REQUIRED TO
PLEASE CONTACT ME TO
REQUEST REFERENCE
INFORMATION.